prestigecasino.com 2012-11-19

# Privacy and Security at Online Casinos

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

2.1  Your personal data (meaning any information about You from which You can be personally identified, such as Your name, address, telephone number or email address, and which is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “ **Your Information** ”), will be processed by the Operator (which include its agents and employees), and (where appropriate) our partners and subcontractors in order to be able to provide the full range of the Services to You. Your Information is collected when You register to open an account with us; or when You submit a written query to us. 

2.2  While the Websites may contain links to websites operated by parties other than the Operator (for example the UK Gambling Commission), the Operator is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any such websites.

2.3  By using any of the Services, You acknowledge that You have read, and agree to, the terms of this Privacy Policy and that, where You provide us with Your Information (including, for the avoidance of doubt, by submitting a query to us through one of the Websites, or where You only partially complete an account registration process), You consent to the use by the Operator (and our partners and subcontractors) of Your Information for the purposes set out in paragraph 3 of this Privacy Policy.

2.4  If You do not wish to provide Your Information on the basis set out in this Privacy Policy You should not enter the relevant information in the spaces provided on the relevant part of any Website, or provide any of Your Information to us over the telephone. However if You do not provide such information, You may not be permitted to make full use of the relevant part of the Services.

2.5  As part of the account registration process, We also offer visitors registering with us the opportunity to “opt out” from keeping them informed of future events, offers and promotions from the Operator. Visitors who wish to take this option should ‘untick’ the relevant box in the registration process. You may update Your marketing preferences at any time through ‘My Account/Update Marketing Preferences’ (or similar) section of the Website (where available) or by contacting Customer Services. If (where available) You have chosen to receive information on future events, offers and promotions by SMS message to Your cellular telephone, You may “opt out” of receiving such information at any time by replying with the word “STOP”.

 **WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

3.1  The Operator collects Your Information in order to:

3.1.1  Enable us to set up Your Account so that You can make full use of all of the features of the Services, including crediting Your account with funds, placing bets and playing games;

3.1.2  Enable us to receive questions and comments from You through our Online Help Centre, and for us to be able to respond to them;

3.1.3  Comply with relevant regulations regarding Your registration, for example completing age verification checks; and

3.1.4  (provided that You do not “opt out” from this option), to keep You informed of future events, offers and promotions from the Operator.

3.2  In addition to the broad purposes identified in paragraph 3.1 above, the Operator will only use Your Information, including sharing Your Information with our third party partners and subcontractors who process data (including, where appropriate, Your Information) on our behalf, for:

3.2.1  setting up, operating and managing Your Account; 

3.2.2  providing any of the Services which are requested of us, and for any proper purpose connected with such provision;

3.2.3  verifying the accuracy of Your Information, including disclosure of such information to third parties (including financial institutions, age verification, and credit reporting agencies) in connection with such purposes (a record of the search will be retained and the third party may use the information to assist other companies for verification purposes); 

3.2.4  preparing statistics related to the use of the Services by You and other customers; 

3.2.5  to prepare and display appropriate individualised marketing material and content; 

3.2.6  periodically sending account holders written communications to announce important service changes, technical issue updates and changes to the Terms of Use (which includes this Privacy Policy); 

3.2.7  complying with our regulatory duties, obligations and responsibilities under the under the Gambling Act 2005 and to the Gibraltar Regulatory Authority; and under the relevant legislation and to the relevant regulators in the other jurisdictions where the Operator carries out a regulated activity; 

3.2.8  conforming to legal requirements or complying with legal processes or acting to protect the interests of sporting bodies or other qualified bodies; 

3.2.9  the investigation of suspected unlawful, fraudulent or other improper activity connected with the Services;

3.2.10  the reporting of a crime or suspected crime, including money laundering or any fraud; and

3.2.11  any other purpose which is necessary for the performance of our contractual obligations to You. 

3.3  The Operator will not send You unsolicited information regarding any third party commercial offers or advertisements.

3.4  The Operator may use Your username and/or first name and region for advertising or promotional purposes. 

3.5  Telephone calls to and from our Customer Services Department are recorded for training and security purposes.

3.6  We may transfer Your Information in the event of that we transfer or sell our business or any part of it; including in the event of insolvency.

3.7  If at any time You wish us to stop processing Your Information for the above purposes, then You must contact us and we will take the appropriate steps to stop doing so. Please note that this may mean that Your Account will have to be closed.
